A revenger's tale.
The Assignment is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Walter Hill.
Ace assassin Frank Kitchen is double crossed by gangsters and falls into the hands
of rogue surgeon known as The Doctor who turns him into a woman.
The hitman, now a hitwoman, sets out for revenge, aided by a
nurse named Johnnie who also has secrets.
Frank Kitchen / Tomboy, played by Michelle Rodriguez.
Dr. Rachel Kay, played by Sigourney Weaver.
Dr. Ralph Galen, played by Tony Shalhoub.
Johnnie, played by Caitlin Gerard.
Honest John Hartunian, played by Anthony LaPaglia.
Paul Wincott, played by Paul McGillion.
The Assignment (also known as Tomboy, Revenger (in Australia) and formerly known as (Re) Assignment and Tomboy: A
Revenger's Tale) is an action crime thriller film directed by Walter Hill and co-written by Hill and Denis Hamill.
The film stars Michelle Rodriguez, Tony Shalhoub, Anthony
LaPaglia, Caitlin Gerard, and Sigourney Weaver.
The film had its world premiere at the Toronto
International Film Festival on September 11, 2016.
It was released on March 3, 2017, through video on demand, prior to
a limited release on April 7, 2017, by Saban Films.
The film explores themes of assassin, gangster,
sex change, revenge, mad surgeon.
The tone is intense.